James Earle and Laura Gardin Fraser Papers
James Earle and Laura Gardin Fraser Papers
- Glass negatives
  - Fraser Lantern Slide Collection
    - Title Slides (with names and dates of artists), 40 slides (Oversize 24)
Gardin, Alice Tilton 1927 Nov-1939 Jan (9, to Fraser) 1915 (1, to LGF) 1899 Oct 22 (1, to Theodore Tilton) n.d. (1, to unidentified)
Gardin, John E. 1912 Feb-1919 Aug (4, to Fraser)
Garland, Hamlin 1927 Apr 20 (1, to Edith J.R. Isaacs)
Gibson, Charles Dana 1918 May-1941 Jan (8, to Fraser)
Gilbert, Cass 1924 Oct-1934 Dec (5, to Fraser)
Gosoy, Emily G. 1934 Dec-1935 Jan (2, to Fraser)
Grant, Ulysses III (5, to Fraser)
Grimes, Frances 1926 Apr 10, n.d. (2, to Fraser)
Grosvenor, Melville B. 1951 Jan-1953 Jan (5, to LGF) - filed under Business Records: National Geographic Society (Box 18)
Gugler, Anne 1937 Mar-1937 Apr (2, to LGF)
Gugler, Eric 1932 Aug-1948 Jul (9, to Fraser) 1948 May-1948 Aug (2, to Fraser) - filed under Business Records: Franklin, Benjamin, seated figure (Boxes 14, 15) 1931 Nov 24 (1, to Fraser) - filed under Business Records: Edison, Thomas Alva, seated figure (Boxes 13, 14) 1949 Jul-1949 Dec (3, to Fraser) - filed under Business Records: Patton, Gen. George S. Jr., (West Point) (Box 19)
Hagedorn, Herman 1929 Nov-1953 Oct (6, to Fraser)
Hamlin, Mrs. Whelyn 1932 Jan-1932 Jul (6, to Fraser)
Hansen, Harry 1927 Apr 25 (1, to EAR)
Harding, Ann 1922-1953 Oct (34, to Fraser)
Harding, Ann 1927 (1, to unidentified)
Harriman, Averell 1958 Jul 31 (1, to Fraser)
Harriman, Mary W. 1925 Jun-1927 Mar (2, to Fraser)
Harriman, Roland 1943 Jul-1953 Oct (7, to Fraser)
Hazlitt, Henry 1927 (1, to Edith J.R. Isaacs)
Helm, Edith 1937 Mar 10-27 (7, to Fraser)
Henri, Robert 1919 Dec 8, n.d. (2, to Fraser)
Hewlett, J. Monroe 1930 Apr 9 (1, to Fraser)
Hoffman, Malvina 1928 Nov 3 (1, to Fraser) 1951 May 23 (1, to Fraser) - filed under Business Records: National Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, Gold Medal (Box 18)
Hoover, Lou Henry 1931 Jun 19 (1, to Fraser) 1931 Jun 22 (1, to Charles Moore)
Howe, Mark Anthony 1945 Nov 25 (1, to Fraser)
Hurst, Fannie 1927 (1, to Edith J.R. Isaacs)
Huntington, Anna Hyatt 1946 Jun-1956 Dec (9, to Fraser) 1954 Apr-1954 Dec (6, to LGF) - filed under Business Records: Pegasus (Box 19)
Huntington, Archer 1926 Apr-1953 Jun (7, to Fraser)
Huntington, Archer 1948 Jul 15 (1, to LGF) 1927 Apr 20 (1, to Edith J.R. Isaacs) 1926 Feb-1930 May (7, to JEF) - filed under Business Records: American Geographical Society (Box 11)
Johnson, Robert U. 1929 May-1936 Oct (13, to Fraser)
Keating, Joseph A. 1932 Jan 15 (1, to Fraser)
Kent, Henry Watson 1918 May-1933 Jun (5, to Fraser)
Keppel, Frederick 1919 Jan-1934 May (5, to Fraser)
Lawrie, Lee 1930 Apr-1953 Oct (20, to Fraser) 1947 Dec 8 (1, to Fraser) - filed under Business Records: Gallatin, Albert (Box 15) 1937 May 18 (1, to Fraser) - filed under Business Records: Washington, George, standing figure (Box 21)
Ledoux, Louis F. 1919 Jan-1947 Apr (7, to Fraser)
Lippmann, Walter 1927 May 2 (1, to Edith J.R. Isaacs)
Lodge, John 1949 Nov-1953 Oct (3, to Fraser) 1951 May 29 (1, to Fraser) - filed under Business Records: National Institute of Arts and Letters (Box 18)
Low, Will Hicok 1924 Jul 24 (1, to Fraser)
McAdoo, William G. 1919 Nov 21 (1, to JEF)
Manship, Paul 1930 Jan-1953 Nov (11, to Fraser)
Marquis, Don 1927 Apr 26 (1, to Edith J.R. Isaacs)
Mellon, Andrew W. 1927 May 4 (1, to JEF)
Minnigerode, C.P. 1930 Feb-1930 May (4, to Fraser)
Mohler, A.L. 1915 May-1915 Jul (2, to Fraser)
Moore, Charles 1924 Nov-1942 Nov (18, to Fraser) 1928 Sep 28 (1, to JEF) - filed under Business Records: Bacon, Robert, bust (Box 13) 1922 Nov-1935 Dec (20, to JEF) - filed under Business Records: Com. of Fine Arts (Box 13) 1928 Oct-1929 Sep (10, to LGF) - filed under Business Records: Lindbergh, Chas., medal (Box 17)
Noguchi, Isamu 1930 Nov 17 (1, to Fraser) - filed under Business Records: Guggenheim, John S. Memorial Foundation (Box 15)
Patton, Beatrice 1946 Feb-1953 Sep (33, to JEF) - filed under Business Records: Patton, Gen. George F. Jr. (Boxes 18, 19) 1951 May (3, to JEF) - filed under Business Records: National Institute of Arts and Letters (Box 18) 1947 Nov-1952 Nov (5, to JEF and LGF) - filed under Business Records: Patton, Gen. George F. Jr. (Boxes 18, 19) 1950 Jun-1953 May (6, to LGF) - filed under Business Records: Patton, Gen. George F. Jr. (Boxes 18, 19) 1948 May 22 (1, to Paul Harkins) - filed under Business Records: Patton, Gen. George F. Jr. (Boxes 18, 19)
Patton, Maj. G.S. 1962 Jan 23 (1, to LGF) - filed under Business Records: American History Panels (Box 11)
Phelps, William Lyon 1927 Apr-1927 May (2, to Edith J.R. Isaacs)
Pollard, John G. 1930 Jun 27 (1, to Fraser)
Pope, John Russell 1934 Jul-1937 Apr (4, to Fraser)
Pratt, George D. 1927 Nov-1933 Mar (17, to Fraser)
Robinson, Edwin Arlington (to ATG, 49) undated (2 items) 1922 May 19 1923 May 16 1924 Jun 14 1924 Aug 2 1924 Sep 21 1924 Sep 30 1924 Oct 7 1925 Mar 17 1925 Apr 11 1925 May 20 1925 Nov 7 1926 Apr 30 1926 Jun 13 1926 Aug 22 1927 Jun 2 1927 Jul 1 1927 Jul 28 1927 Oct 13 1928 Apr 11 1928 May 2 1928 Jun 21 1928 Aug 14 1928 Nov 16 1929 Mar 17 1929 Apr 7 1929 Apr 21 1929 May 20 1929 Jun 8 1929 Aug 11 1929 Sep 16 1929 Oct 17 1929 Nov 26 1930 Apr 6 1930 May 11, transcription only 1930 Jun 1 1930 Jul 13 1930 Aug 5 1930 Sep 4 1930 Nov 9 1931 May 11 1931 Nov 17 1932 Apr 1 1932 May 3 1932 Jun 10 1933 Apr 10 1933 Sep 4 1934 Aug 10 1934 Oct 23
Robinson, Edwin Arlington (to JEF, 34) undated (2 items) 1913 Jun 9 1913 Jun 22 1913 Dec 9 1917 Feb 23 1917 Dec 9 1919 Nov 8 1921 Jul 13 1922 Jul 23 1923 Jul 11 1923 Jul 25 1923 Sep 17 1923 Oct 15 1924 May 24 1925 Nov 1 1926 Jul 6 1926 Sep 10 1926 Nov 19 1927 Jan 26 1927 Nov 30 1928 Apr 11 1928 Jun 1 1928 Aug 13 1928 Aug 25 1928 Sep 17 1929 Jun 20 1931 Jun 29 1931 Jun 29 1931 Jun 30 1932 Jun 27 1932 Jul 16 1932 Oct 20 1933 Dec 15 1934 Dec 30
Robinson, Edwin Arlington (to LGF, 122) Undated Undated fragment, transcription only 1916 Feb 7 1916 Sep 30 1917 Sep 21 1917 Dec 25 1918 Jul 25 1918 Sep 6 1918 Oct 1 1918 Oct 7 1918 Oct 14 1918 Oct 16 1919 Jun 11 1919 Aug 4 1919 Sep 11 1919 Oct 5 1919 Oct 26 1920 Aug 6 1920 Sep 10 1920 Sep 14 1920 Oct 3 1920 Oct 7 1920 Nov 3 1921 Sep 4 1921 Oct 11 1921 Oct 18 1921 Oct 25 1922 May 18 1922 May 29 1922 Jul 31 1922 Sep 17 1922 Oct 4 1923 Oct 7 1924 May 22 1924 Aug 10 1924 Sep 10 1924 Nov 18 1925 Mar 16 1925 Apr 5 1925 Apr 16 1925 May 5 1925 May 18 1925 Jun 10 1925 Jun 13 1925 Jul 21 1925 Aug 16 1925 Sep 10 fragment, transcription only 1925 Sep 20 1925 Oct 7 1925 Nov 15 1925 Nov 24 1925 Dec 3 1926 May 12 1926 May 28 1926 Jun 16 1926 Aug 1 1926 Oct 9 1926 Oct 19 1926 Oct 23 1926 Nov 23 1927 Jan 20 1927 Jan 24 1927 Jan 27 1927 May 11 1927 May 23 1927 Jun 5 1927 Jul 28 1927 Aug 12 1927 Aug 20 1927 Sep 20 1927 Nov 7 1927 Nov 18 1928 May 11 1928 Jul 2 1928 Oct 9 1928 Nov 19 1928 Nov 29 1929 Apr 29 1929 Jul 4 1929 between Jul 4 and Oct 22 1929 Oct 22 1930 Mar 17 1930 Apr 28 1930 Jun 30 1930 Sep 15 1930 Oct 19 1930 Oct 30 1930 Nov 25 1930 Dec 3 1930 Dec 10 1930 Dec 17 1931 Apr 6 1931 Apr 12 1931 May 31 1931 Jul 30 1931 Oct 30 1931 Dec 3 1932 Apr 28 1932 Jun 3 1932 Jun 16 1932 Jun 20 1932 Aug 26 1932 Oct 22 1932 Dec 1 1933 Mar 19 1933 Apr 22 1933 Jun 3 1933 Sep 12 1933 Oct 8 1933 Nov 1 1933 Nov 12 1933 Nov 19 1933 Dec 8 1934 Mar 29 1934 Apr 5 1934 May 9 1934 Jul 4 1934 Sep 11 1934 Nov 13 1934 Nov 25 1934 Dec 9 1934 Dec 16
Robinson, Edwin Arlington (to JEF and LGF, 3) 1923 Jun 20 1925 May 6 1933 Dec 19
Robinson, Edwin Arlington (to JEF, LGF and ATG, 2) 1923 Apr 23 1929 Dec 1
Romulo, Carlos P. 1950 Oct-1952 Dec (2, to JEF) - filed under Business Records: End of the Trail (Box 14)
Roosevelt, Edith K. 1938 Jun 23 (1, to Fraser) 1938 Jun 15 (1, to JEF) - filed under Business Records: Roosevelt, Theodore, equestrian figure (Box 20)
Roosevelt, Eleanor 1933 Apr-1944 Oct (7, to Fraser)
Roosevelt, Kermit 1927 Apr 20 (1, to Edith J.R. Isaacs) 1938 Jun 17 (1, to JEF) - filed under Business Records: Roosevelt, Theodore, equestrian figure (Box 20)
Roosevelt, Theodore Jr. 1938 Jun 16 (1, to JEF) - filed under Business Records: Roosevelt, Theodore, equestrian figure (Box 20)
Root, Elihu 1919 Jun-1930 Apr (4, to Fraser)
Ross, Nellie T. 1946 Aug-1952 Jan (4, to Fraser)
Rubins, David 1951 May 20 (1, to JEF) - filed under Business Records: National Institute of Arts and Letters (Box 18)
Sabin, Florence 1933 Apr 3 (1, to LGF)
Saint Gaudens, Augustus 1902 Oct-1908 Sep (17, to Fraser)
Saint Gaudens, Augusta H. 1915 Sep-1919 Jul (2, to Fraser)
Saint Gaudens, Homer 1929 Jun-1943 Jun (12, to Fraser) 1927 Mar 17 (1, to JEF) - filed under Business Records: Chien Blessé by Frémiet (Box 13) 1947 Jul-1948 Jan (11, to JEF) - filed under Business Records: Saint Gaudens, Augustus, memorial (Box 20) 1927 Feb 26 (1, to LGF) - filed under Business Records: Chien Blessé by Frémiet (Box 13)
Sawyer, Mrs. Oliver 1923 Sep-1957 Oct (29, to Fraser)
Schoellkopf, Paul 1927 Jan 3 (1, to Fraser)
Skinner, Cornelia 1923 (1, to Fraser)
Swartwout, E. 1929 Sep-1937 Oct (3, to Fraser)
Taft, Lorado 1918 Jun-1932 Apr (2, to Fraser)
Tilton, Theodore 1882 Feb 4 (1, to unidentified)
Trowbridge, Alexander 1928 May-1928 Oct (2, to Fraser)
Vanamie, Grace D. 1927 Nov-1935 Oct (3, to Fraser)
Walcott, Frederic 1937 Nov 3 (1, to Fraser)
Walter, James J. 1927 Jul 19 (1, to Fraser)
Watrous, Harry 1918 Apr-1928 Jul (2, to Fraser)
Waugh, Sidney B. 1951 May 26 (1, to JEF) - filed under Business Records: National Institute of Arts and Letters (Box 18)
Weinman, Adolph A. 1928 May-1947 Aug (4, to Fraser) 1950 Aug 23 (1, to JEF)
Widener, Joseph 1928 Sep 24 (2, to LGF) - filed under Business Records: "Fairplay" (Box 14)
Wilder, Thornton 1928 Dec 17 (1, to EAR)
Williams, Wheeler 1948 Jan-1964 Oct (6, to Fraser)
Woollcott, Alexander 1937 Feb 24-25 (2, to LGF)